(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T22:57:14.441755",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます
部屋を明るくし画面から十分離れてご視聴ください
*This broadcast contains scenes with intense flashing lights.
Please watch in a well-lit room and stay a safe distance from the screen.
店長 兎田
[Store Manager: Usada]
朝礼
[Morning Meeting]
まもなく！
[Starting Soon!]
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませー！
Welcome, welcome! Come on in, everyone!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you so much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませー！
Welcome, welcome! Come right on in!
本日はお忙しい中、数ある配信の中から当配信、
Thank you all so much for taking time out of your busy day,
兎田ぺこら7周年記念LIVEをご指名いただき、ご閲覧いただき誠にありがとうございます！
and choosing to tune in to Usada Pekora's 7th Anniversary 3D Live!
日頃のご愛顧にお応えいたしまして、兎田ぺこらオリジナルのステージを取り揃えましてのお出迎え、
To show our gratitude for your continued support, we welcome you to this original Usada Pekora stage,
お祭り騒ぎでゲストもたくさんでお送りいたします！
bringing you a festival of fun packed with plenty of special guests!
玉の方もメダルの方も全て超・超・超！
All our balls and medals are super, super, super recommended today,
オススメでお出迎えとなっておりますれば、
so to all our valued guests,
どちらのお客様も最後までジャンジャンバリバリとお楽しみくださいませ！
please keep hitting the jackpot and enjoying the rush until the very end!
日頃ご自慢の右腕、左腕により一層の磨きをかけましてで、
Put those prized left and right arms of yours to good use,
しっかりとガッチリとコメントもしてくださいませ！
and be sure to shower us with lots and lots of comments!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませー！
Welcome, welcome! Come on in, everyone!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ～！
Now then, welcome, welcome, welcome!
本日も様々な景品... グッズをご用意しております！
Today as well, we have prepared various prize—merchandise!
[グッズ：活動7周年記念]
[Merchandise: Activity 7th Anniversary Commemoration]
ぜひ本日のライブの思い出におひとついかがでしょうか！
How about picking one up as a memento from today's live?
1つ目の目玉商品はこちら！
The first featured item is this!
アクリルパネル！こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
The acrylic panel! This was illustrated by Ina-chan from Hololive English!
とってもレア、とってもレア、そしてかわいいぺこらをありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
It's super rare, super rare, and thank you for such a cute Pekora! Thank you so much!
イナ、ありがとうイナ！
Ina, thank you, Ina!
是非とも皆さんのデスクトップ周りに置くといいぺこですね～
It would be wonderful to display this around your desktop, peko~
2つ目はこちら！
The second item is this!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！イラストはまるえり先生に描いてもらいました！
Random acrylic keychains! The illustrations were drawn by Marueri-sensei!
めちゃめちゃかわいいぺこですね～
They are super cute, peko~
是非とも全種揃えたくなってしまう、そんなランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
You'll definitely want to collect them all—these random acrylic keychains!
どれが来るかは届いてからのお楽しみぺこです！
Finding out which one you get once it arrives is the fun part, peko!
3つ目はぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
The third item is a "Uso peko desho..." T-shirt handwritten by Pekora!
この暑い夏を乗り切るのにピッタリなTシャツ！
The perfect T-shirt to get through this hot summer!
「うそぺこでしょ…」の場面がきっとある、そんな時に着たいTシャツぺこですね！
There will definitely be "Uso peko desho..." moments, and this is the T-shirt to wear then, peko!
4つ目はトラックジャケット！
The fourth item is the track jacket!
こちらもまた最高にかっこいいぺこですね！
This is also incredibly cool, peko!
後ろにはキービジュアルのぺこら！
On the back is the key visual Pekora!
この中に「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ、そしてジャケットを羽織ってお家にいったら最高～！
Wearing the "Uso peko desho..." T-shirt under this jacket and heading home would be the absolute best!
お出かけにもちょうどいいぺこですね！
It's also just right for going out, peko!
そしてなんと、なんと！フルセットをご購入の方には更なる特典がございます！こちら！
And what's more, what's more! Those who buy the full set get an extra bonus! Here it is!
数量限定でぺこらの直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
In limited quantities, a postcard with Pekora's handwritten autograph & foil-stamped message is included!
以上、是非皆様じゃんじゃんばりばりゲットしてください！
That's all! Everyone, please go ahead and grab lots of them!
兎田ぺこらに夢と希望と未来を乗せまして、配信終了のお声がかかりますまで、
Entrusting Usada Pekora with dreams, hopes, and the future, until the stream end announcement is made,
一気にじゃんじゃんばりばりと最終最後のお時間までご視聴くださいませ！
please watch with all your energy right up to the very end!
[私バージョンアップ！ / 作詞・作曲：ユニバーサルサウンドチーム]
[Song: Watashi Version Up! / Lyrics & Composition: UNIVERSAL SOUND TEAM]
Ah 潮風に誘われて
Ah, beckoned by the sea breeze,
はしゃぐ声 波の音 近づいてゆく
playful voices and the sound of waves draw near.
Ah 高い空 白い雲
Ah, the high sky and white clouds,
まぶしい海と恋の季節
a dazzling ocean and a season of romance.
日に焼けた あなたが笑っていた
Sun-tanned, you were smiling.
たくさんの光がキラキラ
Countless beams of light sparkle brightly.
コイするココロで 変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a loving heart, a lucky day begins to change.
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our joined hands are enchanted by magic.
笑ってばっかり ここは夏の国
Nothing but laughter here in this land of summer.
私をバージョンアップ！
Version me up!
Ah 照らし出す太陽が
Ah, the sun shining down
まぶしくて かき氷 イチゴえらんで
is so dazzling, choosing strawberry shaved ice.
Ah 青い空 白い砂
Ah, blue skies, white sands,
コントラストなピンクのくち
contrasting with pink lips.
染まってく くちびる 照れ笑い
Lips getting stained, a bashful smile.
誘ってるみたいで ドキドキ
Like an invitation, making my heart flutter.
コイするココロが スピードあげてく
A heart in love picks up speed.
見つめるヒトミが 大胆になるよ
The eyes gazing at me are growing bolder
言葉はいらない 今を感じたい
We don't need words, I just want to feel this moment
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
夕陽を映す海は オレンジ
The sea reflecting the setting sun turns orange
二人のシルエット
Our two silhouettes
足をさらう 星の砂
Star sand sweeping around our feet
そっと、ねぇ 連れてって遠くに
Gently, hey, take me far away
コイするココロは もう止まらない！
This heart in love won't stop anymore!
合わせた手のひら 合図を送るよ
Bringing our palms together, sending you a signal
何もいらない ふたりだけの国
I need nothing else in a world just for the two of us
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
コイするココロで 変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a heart in love, this lucky day starts to change
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our held hands are falling under a spell
笑ってばっかり ここは夏の国
Doing nothing but laughing, this is a land of summer
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
私のブランニュー・デイ！！！
It's my brand new day!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はーい、みんなぺこらのライブに来てくれてアリぺこでしたー！
Alright! Thank you so much everyone for coming to Pekora's live!
1曲目は「私バージョンアップ！」でしたー！
The first song was "Watashi Version Up!"
1曲目当てた人いますかー？
Did anyone guess the first song?
何のね、曲が来るか、みんなね、たくさん考えてくれたと思うけど、
I bet you all thought a lot about what song would come,
まずは1曲目は「私バージョンアップ！」でした。
but the very first song was "Watashi Version Up!"
ということで、今回も兎田ぺこら、パチンコスロットライブ、第3弾！
And so, this is once again Usada Pekora's Pachinko & Slot Live, Part 3!
イェーイ、イェイ、イェイ、イェーイ！
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
ということで、おいおい、ぺこちゃん、
So I know you might say, "Hold on, Peko-chan,
前回も前々回もパチンコスロットライブだったじゃん！
you did pachinko and slot lives the last two times as well!
なんで3回目もやるんだよ！
Why are you doing it a third time?!"
って思いましたよね？はい、私も、
you thought that, right? Yes, even I thought,
3回目はやりすぎか、さすがにやりすぎてるぺこなのかなーって思ったんですけども、
"Is a third time too much? Maybe I'm overdoing it..."
こちら見てください。
But please take a look at this!
はい、兎田ぺこら7周年記念ライブということで、
Yes, this is the Usada Pekora 7th Anniversary Live, so...
「7」なんです。
It's all about "7"!
「7」と言ったらやるしかないよね！そうぺこだよね！ということで、
When you think of "7", you gotta do it, right? Of course you do! So...
今回もやらせてください。
Please let me do it again this time!
めちゃめちゃね、いい曲たくさんあるぺこですので、絶対みんなも楽しんでもらえる、
There are so many amazing songs, so you all will definitely have a blast!
それだけは自信があるぺこなので、
I'm completely confident about that,
ぜひともお楽しみに。そして、
so please look forward to it! And...
ハッシュタグのね、「#兎田ぺこら7周年記念LIVE」もたくさん呟いてくださーい！
please tweet a lot using the hashtag #兎田ぺこら7周年記念LIVE!
ということで、ここからはみんなお楽しみのゲストパート！
With that said, from here begins the guest segment everyone's been waiting for!
今年はどんな方が来るのか、お楽しみにー！
Look forward to seeing who will be joining us this year!
兎神拳に二対一の戦いはない
In Rabbit Divine Fist, there is no two-on-one battle!
覇王はこの拳王ただ一人！
The supreme ruler is this Fist King alone!
北兎無双
[Hokuto Musou]
DESTINY STAR
静寂の闇を 溶かす瞬き
A twinkling light that dissolves the darkness of silence,
星座のStory 語りかければ
when speaking of the constellations' story,
それぞれの想い 弾かれるように
as if strummed by each and every feeling,
男達の旅は始まる
the journey of men begins.
乾き果てて ひび割れてく時代で
In an era that's parched and cracking apart,
たった1つの 信じるものを
seeking after the one single thing
追い求めてく
they can believe in...
輝く Destiny star
Shining Destiny star,
導かれて 野望の果てまで
guided all the way to the edge of ambition,
譲れない願い 向き合う時
when unyielding wishes face one another,
運命始まる
destiny begins.
(Go straight) 数えきれない
(Go straight) Gaze upon the countless...
(Far away) 悲しみを見つめ
(Far away) ...sorrows,
光放つ Destiny star
and shine your light, Destiny star.
いつも予言には 「答え」しかない
In prophecies, there are only "answers."
辿る道は 自分次第で
The path you tread depends on yourself,
進むべき明日を 切り拓くよう
so to carve open the tomorrow they must take,
男達は戦い続ける
the men continue to fight.
命さえも 投げ出しても構わない
"I wouldn't care even if I threw my life away"—
そう思えるほど 守りたいもの 見つけた日から
ever since the day I found something I want to protect that much.
囁く Destiny star
Whispering Destiny star,
迷い捨てて 悪夢の果てまで
casting aside doubts to the end of the nightmare,
一歩も引けない プライドから
from a pride that won't give a single step,
火花が飛び散る
sparks scatter into flight.
(Go straight) まだ遠くても
(Go straight) Even if it's still far away,
(Far away) その手を伸ばして
(Far away) reach out your hand,
つかまえてよ Destiny star
and seize it, Destiny star!
絆確かめ 未来の扉
Confirming our bond, opening the door to the future,
開けて旅立つ
and setting off on a journey.
輝く Destiny star
Shining Destiny star,
導かれて 野望の果てまで
guided all the way to the edge of ambition,
譲れない願い 向き合う時
when unyielding wishes face one another,
運命始まる
destiny begins.
(Go straight) 数えきれない
(Go straight) Gaze upon the countless...
(Far away) 悲しみを見つめ
(Far away) ...sorrows,
光放つ Destiny star
and shine your light, Destiny star.
Destiny star
激熱！
Super hot!
チャンスぺこ！
Chance-peko!
激熱ぺこ！！！
Super hot-peko!
ここまでじゃ、ぺこの助！
This is the end for you, Pekonosuke!
恨みに歪んだ剣でぺこーらは討てぬぺこよ！
You cannot strike down Pekora with a blade twisted by grudge-peko!
紅い雫 滲む唇に
Upon lips stained with crimson drops,
ふわり 嘆きの霧 触れてゆく
a mist of lament softly brushes past.
空に浮かぶ鏡 美しく
The mirror floating in the sky shines beautifully,
遥か暗夜の彼方 照らしてる
illuminating the far side of the dark night.
降り注ぐ数多の星に想い馳せて
Turning my thoughts to the countless raining stars,
しめやかに 深い絆の
quietly, the deep bond's...
強く 強く 結ぶ
Tying tightly, ever so tightly,
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Brilliant eyes shining in lapis lazuli,
闇よりの使いに閉ざされても
Even if they are shut out by messengers of darkness,
繋いだ夢の橋 誰も奪えないから
No one can ever take away the bridge of dreams we connected,
無限の明日映して
Reflecting an infinite tomorrow.
妖し光放つ鳴神に
To the thunder god radiating an enchanting glow,
甘い言葉の蜜 薫り立つ
The honey of sweet words wafts through the air.
密か 黒い鼓翼 忍び寄る
Secretly, dark fluttering wings creep closer,
心臓-鐘-が行き場求め
As the heartbeat bell tolls,
叩き出す
searching for a place to go.
星霜の流れに隠す 歪んだ思惑
Hiding twisted schemes within the passage of time,
艶やかに鋭い牙を剥く
Fascinatingly baring sharp fangs.
巡る 巡る 悲劇
Tragedies repeat again and again,
玉響に消えゆく水泡のように
Like bubbles vanishing in the blink of an eye.
儚い物語-とき-辿る運命なら
If we are fated to trace such fleeting moments,
曇りなき刀 掲げ 清い詩紡ぐ
I'll raise a spotless blade and weave a pure song,
譲れぬ未来のため
For the sake of an unyielding future.
浅い眠り続く黎明に
In the dawn following a restless slumber,
独り祈り込めて織り上げた
I poured my solitary prayers into what I wove.
涙 蒼い雲に刻まれて
Tears etched into the azure clouds,
愛しあなたの影追いかける
I chase after the shadow of my beloved.
憎しみの炎渦巻くこの地上で
On this earth where flames of hatred swirl,
汚れなき心 貫いてく
I will carry through with an unblemished heart,
熱き 熱き 誓い
With a burning, passionate oath.
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Brilliant eyes shining in lapis lazuli,
闇よりの使いに閉ざされても
Even if they are shut out by messengers of darkness,
繋いだ夢の橋 悠久に綴りゆく
We will weave this connected bridge of dreams for eternity,
奏でる 奇跡 きっと...
Surely bringing forth a miracle...
可能性の兎
[The Rabbit of Possibility]
兎田ぺこら 変身まで
[Until Usada Pekora's Transformation]
未来ある若者の芽を摘むな！
Don't nip the buds of youth who have a future!
後ろ向くなお前！前だけ見てろ人生！
Don't look back! Look only forward in life!
ぺこちゃんのことが、大好きです！
I love Peko-chan so much!
覚醒
[Awakening]
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
時の鼓動がまだ響く間
While the pulse of time still echoes,
裸の言葉胸に閉じこめた
I locked these naked words deep in my heart.
記憶の色が滲み始める
The colors of memory begin to blur
破れた世界の隅で
in the corner of this torn world.
何も求めずにただ抱き寄せる
Without seeking anything, I just hold you close.
今の僕にはそれしか出来ない
That is all I can do right now.
震えた強がりでもプライドに見える
Even trembling bluff looks like pride,
逸れた子供のように
like a lost child.
最後の声さえも
Even the last sound of your voice
風がさまようせいで消された
was erased by the wandering wind.
月に手を向けたまま
With hands reaching toward the moon,
君は空の星に消えた
you vanished into the stars in the sky.
「側にいて」と抱きしめても
Even if I hold you close, saying "stay with me,"
もう2度と聞こえない君の歌声は
your singing voice will never be heard again.
降り注いだ雨のサイレン
Like a siren of pouring rain,
僕の代わりに今この空が泣き続ける
the sky weeps on in my place.
これまで踏みつけてきた教えを
The teachings I've trampled on until now,
今掻き集めこの胸に当てても
even if I gather them up against my chest,
救い求め歌うようなお遊戯に見える
it just looks like play, singing for salvation,
物語る大人のように
like adults recounting stories.
言葉に寄り添うだけの
Merely leaning against empty words,
空の愛と導きはいらない
I have no need for hollow love and guidance.
飾られた祈りでは
With decorated prayers,
明日の手掛かりに触れない
we cannot reach a clue to tomorrow.
いつか君に届くはずの
The selfishness drawn by this nameless, youthful poem,
名も無き幼い詩が描くわがままを
which was meant to reach you someday—
忘れたいよ一度だけ
I just want to forget it once,
眠れぬ悲しみがその詩を抱きしめてる
as sleepless sorrow embraces that poem.
Freezing cold shatters my sorrow
And scorching sand puts it together again
投げ捨てられる正しさなら
If it's a righteousness that can be cast away,
消える事ない間違いの方が良い
an indelible mistake would be far better.
臆病に隠してた声を今
The voice I timidly hid away,
この手でもう一度さらせば良い
I should just expose once more with these hands.
掴む軌道も咲く光も
The trajectory we grasp and the blooming light
乾いた心のせいでモノクロに見えた
looked monochrome because of my parched heart.
忘れないよ今日の景色を
I won't forget today's view.
ありふれた願いが足元を照らしてくれる
An ordinary wish illuminates the path at our feet.
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
ふぅ… ぺこーら… 一体どうなったぺこ…？
Whew... what on earth happened to Pekora, peko...?
一匹残らず…
Every last one of them...
喰らってやる
I will devour them!
Crawling inside my head
Shredding my self-control
It's getting close to the edge
I'm breaking down
Fragmented memories are glitching in my head
Stuck in a moment and it's burning up
Bright red, a roaring howl disappears into the night
My soul is here to stay
Woah, woah, woah, woah
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
It's changing me, my heartbeat is racing so fast
Unleashing the carnage inside
"Don't run away now
I'm just getting started"
"Hey now, this ain't who I am"
"Obey now,
the voices confuse my mind"
"Let's go insane now
Look what I've become"
"Obey now to me"
"Your hope's gonna turn to fear"
When I scream
Corrosive voices laugh and whisper in my head
Tried to ignore 'em but they're calling for a bloodshed
I'm like a puppet, someone's pulling all the strings
Drowning in misery, I can't get out
Break out this rusted gate, search and eradicate
Burning the hate from within
"Ready to dominate, it's time to liberate
(The) chaos inside of him"
Woah, woah, woah, woah
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
Straining me, my heartbeat is racing so fast
Unleashing the carnage inside
"Don't run away now
I'm just getting started"
"Hey now, this ain't who I am"
"Obey now,
the voices confuse my mind"
"Let's go insane now
Look what I've become"
"Obey now to me"
"Your hope's gonna turn to fear"
When I scream
Whoa...
ペラペコチャレンジ！
Pera-Peko Challenge!
負けないぺこ！
I won't lose, peko!
伝説の朝に
On the morning of legend,
誓った言葉
the words we swore...
分かち合う声に
In our shared voices,
奇跡よ照らせ
let the miracle shine.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
風の舞うヒカリの空
In the sky of light where the wind dances,
吹き抜ける残響
the lingering echoes blow through.
この右手と
With this right hand,
この左手
and this left hand,
何を求める？
what are we seeking?
魂のカタルシスに
Yearning for the soul's catharsis,
焦がれた感情
these burning emotions—
重ね合えば
if we layer them,
繋ぎ合えば
if we connect them,
伝うのか？
will they reach you?
運命に委ね
Surrendering to destiny,
流れのままに
going with the flow—
変わらぬ明日じゃ
an unchanging vision
面白くない
is no fun at all.
沸騰せよ
Boil up,
血液のレイヴ
rave of blood!
交錯する
Intertwining,
プラズマのように
just like plasma...
革命の
The revolution's
デュアリズム さあ始めよう
dualism—come on, let's begin!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Telepathic roar of life,
届いていますか？
is it reaching you?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love passed down.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the ends of the dream!
どんな人生だって
No matter what path of life,
いつかは交じり合う
they will merge someday.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
On that day, you will make the judgment!
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
プラスマイナスがゼロの
A tuning balanced at zero,
悪くはないチューニング
not bad at all.
キスみたいに
Like a kiss,
クラックした
it cracked open
色褪せないドリーム
an unfading dream.
神様は希望与え
God grants us hope
痛みをぼかして
and blurs the pain.
何を守り
What should I protect?
何を信じ
What should I believe?
生きろと云う？
How do you tell me to live?
未来への扉は
The door to the future
コインのトスさ
is a coin toss.
残酷を選べ
Choose cruelty,
暁の君
you of the dawn.
虹の架かる
Crossing the rainbow,
見た事ない
a never-before-seen
絶景のフライト
breathtaking flight...
教えてやる
I'll show it to you!
覚醒の
The awakening
デュアリズム さあ飛び込もう
dualism—come on, let's dive in!
百花繚乱 ハウル衝動
Profusion of flowers, howling impulse,
火花を散らして
scattering sparks!
胸のブレイブを叩く鼓動
The beat pounding bravery into our chests—
どこまでいけるのか？
how far can we go?
変わらない「ナニカ」で
With an unchanging "something,"
何度クチヅケした
how many times have we kissed?
そして 君は また物語に出会う
And then you meet another story of love...
Just trust my heart
Just feel my heart
Hold you...
誇り高き愛の結晶
Once the proud crystal of love
握りしめたら
is tightly in your grasp,
迎えにゆくから…
I'll come to meet you...
刹那から一生さえ
From a fleeting moment to a lifetime,
すべて見せて来た
I've shown you everything:
君へのLove song
a love song for you.
Break out! 鎖千切って
Break out! Tear off the chains
独立せよ
and claim independence!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Telepathic roar of life,
届いていますか？
is it reaching you?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love passed down.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the ends of the dream!
どんな人生だって
No matter what path of life,
いつかは交じり合う
they will merge someday.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
On that day, you will make the judgment!
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
ヘブンズペコラッシュ、突入ぺこ！
Entering Heaven's Pekorush, peko!
BARを撃ち抜け！
Shoot through the BAR!
まだまだー！
Not over yet!
BARを撃ち抜け！
Shoot through the BAR!
スーパーヘブンズペコラッシュ 突入ペコ！
Entering Super Heaven's Pekorush, peko!
I have a big gun
I took it from my Lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
Been burned in hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Have no prayer
So, I keep the gun with me
For my safety
I'll do it with no sweat
They mean business
No time for sissy pig
Queen of ocean
Sing "the Volga" to you
No need to think about it
You do it or you die
Those aren't tears
Don't let it trick on you
I am hard as steel
Get out of my way
Pay back all at once
Suck away the tender part
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
緊急告知
[Emergency Announcement]
衝撃の
[Shocking]
急展開
[Sudden Development]
みなさん え～...
Everyone... um...
今日は
today...
発表が
I have an announcement...
あります
to make.
大チャンス
Huge chance!
PKRN48
ぺこらんだむぶれいん！叫んじゃえば
Pekorandam Brain! If you shout it out,
事件だ 毎日大変
it's a huge deal, tough every single day!
大抵このためだと 笑えないような笑え
Mostly it's for this, laugh when you can't laugh—
まだペコ！
Not yet, peko!
聞きたくない いいわけバニー
I don't wanna hear it, Excuse Bunny!
地団駄の優柔不断
Stomping your feet in indecision!
みんな楽しい どっちが好き？ 好きなのよ
Everyone's having fun, which one do you like? I love it!
推せ！
Push!
すぐ近くなのに 離れて感じる
Even though you're so close, you feel so far away
君はバスの２つ前の席
You're two seats ahead of me on the bus
声をかけるには ちょっと恥ずかしい
Calling out to you is a little embarrassing
何度 恋をしても 慣れないね
No matter how many times I fall in love, I never get used to it
カーブ曲がり 身体が傾く時
When we turn a curve and our bodies tilt,
その方向は 同じさ
we're leaning in the exact same direction
君に 重力シンパシー 何も話せなくても
Gravitational sympathy with you, even if we don't speak at all,
確かに今 僕らはひとつになる
right now, we are surely becoming one
君に 重力シンパシー 後ろ 気づかなくても
Gravitational sympathy with you, even if you don't notice me behind you,
わかり合える日が来るよ
the day will come when we understand each other
窓が曇るほど 乗客は多く
With so many passengers that the windows fog up,
君の顔が陰で見えなくなる
your face is lost in the shadows
喋るその声に 耳を傾けて
Listening closely to the sound of your voice,
僕は胸の奥をときめかせた
my heart fluttered deep inside
バスが急に スピード上げた瞬間
The moment the bus suddenly sped up,
みんな一緒に仰け反った
we all jolted backward together
愛は 重力フレンズ そこにいるそれだけで
Love is gravitational friends, just by you being there,
２人はそう 地球を共有する
the two of us share this Earth together
愛は 重力フレンズ 存在認知されてなくても
Love is gravitational friends, even if my existence goes unnoticed,
そのベクトル進めばいい
I just have to keep moving forward along that vector
君に 重力シンパシー 何も話せなくても
Gravitational sympathy with you, even if we don't speak at all,
確かに今 僕らはひとつになる
right now, we are surely becoming one
君に 重力シンパシー いつか同じ重さで
Gravitational sympathy with you, someday with equal weight,
愛について想うだろう
you will think about love
みんな！盛り上がっていくぺこよー！
Everyone! Let's get hyped, peko~!
いくよー！ファイヤー！
Here we go! Fire!
お祭りぺこー！
It's a festival, peko!
乙女フェスティバル SPECIAL LIVE！
Otome Festival SPECIAL LIVE!
ラヴィラヴィ小さなビットに
Lovi-lovi, into tiny bits
でっかいアイを交信中！
transmitting massive love!
ちょっと沼っても許してね？
Forgive me even if you get a little obsessed, okay?
いっとくけど愛は非効率！
Just so you know, love is inefficient!
熱響！乙女フェスティバル！
Passionate Resonating Otome Festival!
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom
一度きりの物語
in this once-in-a-lifetime story
ヤマトナデシコ いつだって
Yamato Nadeshiko, always
時代を彩るDreamer
a Dreamer coloring the eras
無限の彼方へ
To the far side of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
恋に焦がれてドキドキ
Yearning for love, my heart is pounding,
（ドキドキ）
(Pounding!)
いじわるなんてイヤイヤ
I hate it when you're mean!
（イヤイヤ）
(No way!)
とびっきりのスマイルで
With my very best smile,
あなたを連れてってあげる
I'll take you along with me!
惹かれちゃうのは運命
Falling for each other is destiny!
（そうそう）
(That's right!)
あれもこれも抱きしめてあげる
I'll embrace each and every part of you!
選ぶ道に誇りあれ
May there be pride in the path you choose!
進めば輝く未来
If you move forward, a bright future awaits!
乙女心
A maiden's heart...
（乙女心）
(A maiden's heart...)
いつだってフェスティバル
It's always a festival!
きらめいて
Sparkle and shine,
トキメキ届けたい
I want to send this excitement to you
今すぐに
Right this very instant!
高く高く
Higher and higher!
（高く高く）
(Higher and higher!)
そびえ立つ壁も
Even the towering walls...
やがて超えてくイメージだけで
Just by picturing overcoming them,
Let's Go! Let's Go!
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom,
一度きりの物語
In a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行く運命だから
Since everything is destined to scatter someday,
やるだけやるんです
We'll give it everything we've got!
笑いましょ 声高く
Let's laugh out loud,
明日の自分に届けたい
Reaching out to who we'll be tomorrow!
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
A Yamato Nadeshiko, always
時代を彩るDreamer
A Dreamer painting the era!
無限の彼方へ
To the far side of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
ワガママだっていいでしょ？
It's okay to be selfish sometimes, right?
（でしょ？でしょ？）
(Right? Right?)
可愛いって言ってなでなで
Tell me I'm cute and pat my head!
（なでなで）
(Pat, pat!)
お気に入りのスカートで
Wearing my favorite skirt,
あなたに飛び込んでみたい
I want to dive right into your arms!
夢見るだけじゃ足りない
Just daydreaming isn't enough!
（ダメダメ）
(No way!)
決める時は迷わず行きましょ
When it's time to choose, go without hesitation!
その手で掴む時まで
Until you seize it with your own hands,
未来へ加速して行こう
Let's accelerate toward the future!
Destiny
（いつか）
(Someday...)
あなたと一緒に
Together with you!
永遠に
For eternity,
触れてみたいずっと
I want to keep feeling it forever,
憧れです♪
That's my dream♪
涙
Tears...
（はらり）
(Falling softly...)
こぼれ落ちる日も
Even on the days they overflow,
本気の愛で振り向かせたい
I want to make you look my way with genuine love!
Going! Going!
花と舞い 夢と生き
Dancing with flowers, living with dreams,
重なり合う物語
An intertwining story.
諦めなんて似合わないから
Giving up just doesn't suit us,
やるしかないでしょ
So we just have to go for it!
期待から 希望へと
From expectation into hope,
願いを鳴り響かせて
Let our wishes resound!
ヤマトナデシコ煌めいて
A Yamato Nadeshiko, gleaming,
高まりを超えるFuture Soldier
A Future Soldier surpassing all heights!
奇跡を信じて
Believe in miracles!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
隠しきれない熱い想いと
With this passionate feeling I cannot conceal,
今を走れ走れ
Run, run through the present!
負けない誓い 一緒に掲げて
Raising our unyielding vow together,
行こう
Let's go!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う
Dancing vividly through this and that,
予感に誘われ
Drawn in by anticipation,
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
Passion ignites and takes flight!
無邪気なままじゃいられない
I can't stay completely innocent forever,
切り開いて見つけたいな
I want to carve a path and discover it...
本当を嘘のない私になって
Becoming my honest, true self!
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom,
一度きりの物語
In a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行く運命だから
Since everything is destined to scatter someday,
やるだけやるんです
We'll give it everything we've got!
笑いましょ 声高く
Let's laugh out loud,
明日の自分に届けたい
Reaching out to who we'll be tomorrow!
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
A Yamato Nadeshiko, always
時代を彩るDreamer
A Dreamer painting the era!
無限の彼方へ
To the far side of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
隠しきれない熱い想いと
With this passionate feeling I cannot conceal,
今を走れ走れ
Run, run through the present!
負けない誓い 一緒に掲げて
Raising our unyielding vow together,
行こう
Let's go!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う
Dancing vividly through this and that,
予感に誘われ
Drawn in by anticipation,
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
Passion ignites and takes flight!
大好きな歌の中なら
If it's in the songs I love,
声にしていいのぺこ…
is it okay for me to give voice to my feelings, peko...?
思い出が強さになった
Memories turned into strength.
君ならば歌えるぺこ
If it's you, you can sing it, peko!
今日という過去が生まれて
As the past known as "today" is born,
未来はどういたいか？
how do you want to be in the future?
描くんだ
Picture it!
心からぺこらは…
From the bottom of my heart, Pekora...
「ありがとう」を
wants to sing
歌ってあげたいんだ
"thank you" to everyone!
始まる歌 始まる鼓動
The beginning of a song, the beginning of a heartbeat
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope echo far and wide
「生きる事を諦めない」と
Proclaiming "I will not give up on living"
示せ 熱き夢の 幕開けを
Show us the opening curtain of a passionate dream
馳せよ この 奇跡に 嘘はない
Burst forth, there is no lie in this miracle
その手は何を掴む為にある？
What are those hands meant to grasp?
たぶん待つだけじゃ叶わない
Just waiting probably won't make it come true
その手は何を守る為にある？
What are those hands meant to protect?
伝う 熱は 明日を 輝かす種火に
The warmth that is passed down becomes a spark that makes tomorrow shine
さあ新時代へ銃爪を引こう
Now, let's pull the trigger toward a new era
伝説の未来へとカウントダウン
Counting down to a legendary future
羽撃きは一人じゃない
You are not alone in your flight
過去を 超えた 先に
Beyond the past,
創るべき歴史が 咲き燃えてる
the history we ought to create is blooming and burning
絆、心、一つに束ね
Uniting our bonds and hearts as one
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope echo far and wide
「信ずる事を諦めない」と
Proclaiming "I will not give up on believing"
唄え 可能性にゼロはない
Sing, for there is no zero in possibilities
飛べよ この 奇跡に 光あれ
Fly forth, let there be light in this miracle
切り裂け まだ見ぬ日に行く為に
Slash through in order to reach a day yet unseen
不可能なんて何一つない
There is nothing whatsoever that is impossible
こんなに心強い事はない
Nothing gives us more courage than this
絶対 絶対 信じ合い ぶっちぎる
Definitely, definitely believing in each other, we'll smash right through
例え闇に吸い込まれそうになって
Even if we seem about to be swallowed by darkness
涙さえも血に濡れて苦しくっても
Even if our tears are drenched in blood and it's painful
帰る場所が待っている
A place to return to is waiting for us
集え 守れ 契れ
Gather, protect, pledge
勇気の 結晶が 奇跡なんだ
This crystal of courage is a miracle
願い、祈り、すべてを背負い
Carrying all hopes and prayers on our backs
本気を超えた 本気の唄
A true song that surpasses all earnestness
痛みなんて 何も怖くない
We're not afraid of any pain at all
滾れ 沸騰せよ この身体
Boil, let this body seethe
翳せ さあ 闇夜に 稲妻を
Hold aloft, now, lightning in the dark night
出会い 笑い合い そして 泣きじゃくり
Meeting, laughing together, and then sobbing
命の 炎も 一緒に 燃やして
Burning the flame of life together as well
五感の 全部が 叫ぶ
All five senses are screaming
愛と 呼べる 程の
To the extent that it can be called love,
眩しく 煌めいた 友の証
a dazzling, glittering proof of friendship
絆、心、一つに束ね
Uniting our bonds and hearts as one
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope resound far and wide,
「信ずる事を諦めない」と
declaring "never give up on believing!"
唄え
Sing!
可能性にゼロはない
Possibility is never zero!
飛べよ
Take flight!
この奇跡に
Upon this miracle,
光あれ
let there be light!
タマランドリゾートへようこそ！
Welcome to Tamaland Resort!
わしわしわしわし… わしが行く！
Wash, wash, wash, wash... Here I go!
タムハーランドとはわしのことだー！
Tamharland means none other than me!
みんな、ライブを見てくれてありぺこ〜！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching the live stream, peko~!
この後、10時15分よりメンバーシップ限定アンコールLIVEがあるぺこ〜！
Coming up next at 10:15, there will be a member-exclusive encore live, peko~!
まだまだぺこらの新衣装見たいぺこだよね！
You all want to see more of Pekora's new outfit, right, peko?
ぺこらも歌も歌いたいし、みんなに新衣装をもっと見てほしい！
Pekora wants to sing more songs too, and I want everyone to see more of my new outfit!
なので是非とも遊びに来てぺこ〜！
So please make sure to come hang out, peko~!
そしてグッズのおさらいです！
And now, let's review the merchandise!
1つ目は、アクリルパネル！
The first item is the acrylic panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！ありがとう、イナ〜！
This one was actually illustrated by Ina-chan from hololive English! Thank you, Ina~!
本当にかわいいぺこ！ぺこらがかっこいいしおしゃれだし！
It's truly so cute, peko! Pekora looks cool and stylish!
是非ともゲットしてみてぺこな！
Please be sure to get one, peko!
2つ目はこちら！ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
The second item is this! The random acrylic keychain!
イラストはまるえり先生に描いてもらいました！
The illustration was drawn by Marueri-sensei!
いや、やっぱ最高なキーホルダー来ました、こちら！
Man, what an amazing keychain we have here!
7をやっぱり3つ揃えたいのが、やっぱ人間の性なのかな〜？
Isn't lining up three 7s just human nature, after all?
どうぺこなんでしょうか？
What do you think, peko?
是非とも何が届くかお楽しみに！
Please look forward to seeing which one you get!
そして3つ目は、ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
And the third item is the "You gotta be peko-kidding me..." T-shirt handwritten by Pekora!
大人気の直筆Tシャツ「うそぺこでしょ」出ましたー！
The super popular handwritten "You gotta be peko-kidding me" T-shirt is here!
部屋着にね、ぴったりだと思うぺこだし、もう「うそぺこでしょ」Tシャツで
I think it's perfect for loungewear, peko, and going outside wearing this
是非とも外にね出かけるのも全然ありぺこだと思うので、
"You gotta be peko-kidding me" T-shirt is totally fine too, peko,
ぜひチェックしてみてくださーい！
so please check it out!
そして4つ目は、トラックジャケット！
And the fourth item is the track jacket!
キービジュアルのぺこらが着ているのと同じぺこ！
It's the exact same one Pekora is wearing in the key visual, peko!
是非ともぺこらとお揃いで着ませんか〜？
Won't you wear matching outfits with Pekora?
かっこいいしね、なんかおしゃれじゃない？
It looks cool and really stylish, doesn't it?
こちらもね、コンビニ行く時でもいいし、ま、それとも遊びに行く時でもいい！
You can wear this when going to a convenience store, or when hanging out with friends!
部屋着にしてもいい！もうね、たくさん着てもらえたら嬉しいぺこならでは！
You can wear it at home, too! I'd be so happy if you wear it a lot, peko!
要チェックだー！
It's a must-check!
そして、こちらのグッズをフルセットでご購入いただきますと、
And if you purchase the full set of these goods,
数量限定で、ぺこらの直筆サイン&複製メッセージ入りポストカードが付いてくるー！
it comes with a limited-quantity postcard featuring Pekora's authentic autograph and printed message!
是非ともお手に取ってくださーい！
Please be sure to get your hands on it!
最高だー！
This is the best!
待ってましたこの瞬間！
I've been waiting for this moment!
いいですね！いいですね！めっちゃいいですね！
Nice! Nice! Super nice!
熱すぎ注意！
Warning: It's way too hot!
オイヤッ！オイヤッ！オイヤッ！オイヤッ！
Oiya! Oiya! Oiya! Oiya!
キタキタキタキタキタキタキタキタ！
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here!
フゥー！イェーイ！ふーん！たまらん！
Whew! Yeah! Mm, simply irresistible!
アゲアゲ！足りない！
Hype it up! Not enough!
来るのか？来てしまうのかー？！
Is it coming? Is it really coming?!
ゴーゴー！
Go, go!